### Contact

+31 616 721 334 (Mobile) alex@rizzii.net

www.linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-svetoslavov-484a96177 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Front-End Development React.js Software Infrastructure

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Bulgarian (Full Professional)

### Certifications

ICT & Artificial Intelligence Semester 4

ICT Internship Semester 5

ICT & Software Engineering Semester 3

ICT & Software Semester 2

ICT & Software Engineering Semester 1

# Aleksandar Svetoslavov

Web Developer

Eindhoven, North Brabant, Netherlands

## Summary

During my work, I've had the privilege of contributing to the project "Dialogue" developed by KPMG's and "Trefi", a cutting-edge fintech solution by Capital Tool Company. These experiences honed my skills in client communication, team collaboration, and full-stack web development.

I have strong technical skills in deploying microservices for big software projects. using Kubernetes and autoscaling to make sure everything runs smoothly, as well as developing DevOps pipelines focusing on security, performance and automated testing. I'm proficient at prototyping with tools like Figma and Sketch, and also building engaging web applications, covering both front-end and back-end development.

## Experience

Capital Tool Company

2 years 7 months

Web Developer

March 2021 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Amsterdam, North Holland, Netherlands

Full-stack Developer

September 2022 - January 2023 (5 months)

Amsterdam, North Holland, Netherlands

Rizzii Solutions

Founder

September 2023 - Present (1 month)

Eindhoven, North Brabant, Netherlands

#### **AMBITIONED**

Business Development Manager

August 2023 - Present (2 months)

AuxCode Program Analyst January 2019 - March 2021 (2 years 3 months) Sofia, Sofia City, Bulgaria

## Education

Fontys University of Applied Sciences

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (September 2020 - July 2024)